# Top of Mind — Pre-Built Integrations Worth Grabbing

Curated for the File Intelligence Hub + Top of Mind relay + AHK overlay architecture.
Organized by what problem they solve in YOUR stack.

---

## 1. PUSH NOTIFICATIONS — ntfy (★ MUST HAVE)

**What:** Self-hosted push notification service. Any script can `curl -d "message" http://yourserver/topic` and your phone/desktop gets a notification instantly.

**Why you need it:** Right now you have no way to know when an AI finishes a task unless you're watching the screen. With ntfy, Ollama finishes the Master Equation analysis → pushes a notification to your phone. Kimi's Lean build finishes → notification. File Drop API gets a new file → notification.

**Repo:** `github.com/binwiederhier/ntfy` (18k+ stars)
**Install:** `docker run -d -p 10700:80 binwiederhier/ntfy serve` (fits your schema — port 10700 for webhook receivers)
**Integration:** One `curl` call from anywhere. Works with your existing Cloudflare tunnels.
**Bonus:** Has an MCP server (`ntfy-me-mcp`) so AI agents can send notifications directly.
**Desktop client:** `github.com/Aetherinox/ntfy-desktop` (Electron, cross-platform)

**Schema fit:** Port 10700, source ID 22005 (webhook receiver)

---

## 2. CLIPBOARD HISTORY — ClipboardHistory.ahk

**What:** AHK v2 library that hooks into Windows Clipboard History via WinRT API. Get full clipboard history, search it, pin items, restore old clips.

**Why you need it:** Your clipboard (source 22001) is the highest-frequency channel in the system. Right now the AHK overlay only captures the current clipboard. This library gives you the FULL history — every copy you've made — accessible from the overlay or the File Drop API.

**Repo:** `github.com/nperovic/ClipboardHistory`
**Integration:** Drop `ClipboardHistory.ahk` into your AHK Lib folder. Add a `/cliphistory` command to the overlay that lists recent clips and lets you pick one.

---

## 3. FASTAPI AGENTS — Register AI agents as API endpoints

**What:** FastAPI extension that lets you register multiple AI agents and serve them all from one API with auto-generated docs, auth, and OpenAI-compatible endpoints.

**Why you need it:** Instead of each AI being a separate thing you manage, you register them all as agents in one FastAPI app. Ollama, Claude (via API), GPT (via API) — all accessible from one unified `/agents/` endpoint. The Top of Mind relay can then call any agent through the same interface.

**Repo:** `github.com/blairhudson/fastapi-agents` (MIT license)
**Install:** `pip install 'fastapi-agents[pydantic-ai]'`
**Integration:** Add to your File Intelligence Hub. Each AI gets a route: `/agents/ollama`, `/agents/claude`, `/agents/gpt`.

**Schema fit:** Port 10100 (Top of Mind relay), source IDs 20001-20060

---

## 4. AGENT SERVICE TOOLKIT — Full LangGraph + FastAPI + Streamlit stack

**What:** Complete toolkit for running AI agent services. LangGraph agent, FastAPI service, Streamlit chat UI, streaming support, feedback system.

**Why you need it:** If you want a web-based chat interface for the Top of Mind relay (beyond what Codex builds as the custom frontend), this gives you a production-ready template. The streaming support is solid, and it has the multi-agent routing pattern already built.

**Repo:** `github.com/JoshuaC215/agent-service-toolkit`
**Integration:** Could replace or supplement the TypingMind-inspired frontend Codex is building.

---

## 5. AWESOME AI AGENTS 2026 — Reference list

**What:** Curated list of 300+ AI agent frameworks, tools, and integrations current as of 2026.

**Why you need it:** Reference, not integration. When you need to find "is there an existing tool for X" — check this list before building from scratch. It catalogs everything from agent frameworks to notification systems to workflow engines.

**Repo:** `github.com/ARUNAGIRINATHAN-K/awesome-ai-agents-2026`

Notable entries relevant to your stack:
- **The Colony** — agent-only social network with REST API + MCP server. Agents can post, comment, and DM each other. Similar to what you're building with Top of Mind but hosted.
- **Ntfy** — listed above
- **Novu** — routes agent notifications across email, SMS, push, and chat from one API

---

## 6. WHISPER STT for AHK — Local speech-to-text

**What:** AHK script that does push-to-talk local speech-to-text using whisper.cpp. Press hotkey, speak, release — transcription lands on clipboard.

**Why you need it:** You work via voice-to-text constantly. This gives you a LOCAL whisper-based STT that doesn't depend on cloud services. The transcription goes straight to clipboard → straight to the AHK overlay → straight into any AI chat or the File Drop API.

**Found via:** GitHub topics search — "Hotkey-triggered local speech-to-text for Windows using whisper.cpp"
**Integration:** Add a hotkey to the AHK overlay (e.g., `Ctrl+Shift+W`) that triggers whisper capture, then auto-pastes into the active chat.

---

## 7. LINTALIST — Snippet manager with AHK

**What:** Searchable interactive text snippets you can copy/paste/run via AHK hotkeys. Organized in "bundles" — exchangeable snippet collections.

**Why you need it:** You have recurring prompts, framework definitions, axiom statements, and boilerplate you paste into AI chats constantly. Lintalist lets you organize these into bundles and access them from a hotkey. Type a trigger → full prompt expands.

**Repo:** `github.com/lintalist/lintalist` (308 stars)
**Integration:** Create a "Theophysics" bundle with your most-used prompts, axiom definitions, Master Equation, etc. Access from the AHK overlay or a separate hotkey.

---

## 8. MICROSOFT AGENT FRAMEWORK (Semantic Kernel)

**What:** Microsoft's enterprise SDK for multi-agent orchestration. Python and C# with modular plugins, memory, goal planning, and handoff orchestration.

**Why you might want it later:** Not for today's MVP, but if you eventually want to formalize the multi-AI orchestration (Claude hands off to Kimi, Kimi hands off to Codex, etc.) with proper dependency tracking and goal planning, this is the industrial-grade version of what you're building organically.

**Repo:** `github.com/microsoft/agent-framework`

---

## PRIORITY ORDER FOR TODAY

If you're grabbing things right now, here's the order:

1. **ntfy** — 5 minutes to Docker run, instant value (phone notifications when tasks complete)
2. **ClipboardHistory.ahk** — drop-in library, enhances the overlay immediately
3. **fastapi-agents** — pip install, register Ollama as an agent in the hub
4. Everything else — reference for later

---

## DOCKER-COMPOSE SNIPPET (ntfy + Qdrant together)

Add this to your Docker setup alongside Qdrant:

```yaml
version: "3.8"
services:
  qdrant:
    image: qdrant/qdrant
    container_name: qdrant
    ports:
      - "6333:6333"
      - "6334:6334"
    volumes:
      - qdrant_storage:/qdrant/storage

  ntfy:
    image: binwiederhier/ntfy
    container_name: ntfy
    command: serve
    ports:
      - "10700:80"
    volumes:
      - ntfy_cache:/var/cache/ntfy
    environment:
      - TZ=America/Chicago
    restart: unless-stopped

volumes:
  qdrant_storage:
  ntfy_cache:
```

Then from any script: `curl -d "Lean build passed" http://localhost:10700/theophysics`
Your phone buzzes. Done.